<?xml version='1.0'?>
<options>
  <section title='Translation'>
    <frame label='Language'>
      <radio-group name='i18n_translation'>
        <radio label='Danish' value='da'/>
        <radio label='Dutch' value='nl'/>
        <radio label='English (no translation)' value='None'/>
	<radio label='German' value='de'/>
	<radio label='Italian' value='it'/>
	<radio label='Lithuanian' value='lt'/>
	<radio label='Spanish' value='es'/>
	<radio label='Japanese' value='ja'/>
        <radio label='Russian' value='ru'/>
        <radio label='Use the LANG environment variable' value='From LANG'/>
      </radio-group>
      <spacer/>
      <i18n-message/>
    </frame>
  </section>

  <section title='Messages'>
    <label help='1'>All programs have a 'standard error stream' which they can write text messages to. ROX-Session creates such a connection between itself and every program it starts. It displays all the messages it collects this way briefly on screen.</label>
    <frame label='On-screen message log'>
      <label help='1'>You can click button-3 on an error message to switch to the log window display, or use this button:</label>
      <show-log/>
      <spacer/>
      <numentry label='Show messages for:' unit='seconds' min='1' max='30' name='log_time_shown'>Number of seconds to display each message for</numentry>
      <numentry label='Max area for popup display:' unit='%' min='5' max='60' name='log_percent_switch'>Normally, messages are shown overlayed on the screen for a few seconds. If there are a large number of messages (more than this amount of the screen is covered) then the view switches to the window style.</numentry>
    </frame>
  </section>

  <section title='Power'>
    <frame label='Power'>
      <label help='1'>These commands can be selected in the Logout box as alternatives to logging out. The correct settings vary between different systems. You may need to use xsu or sudo with the command if your system doesn't give normal users permission to shutdown the system.</label>
      <spacer/>
      <entry label='Halt command:' name='halt_command'>Likely commands for halting are 'halt' and 'shutdown -t now'</entry>
      <entry label='Reboot command:' name='reboot_command'>Likely rebooting commands are 'reboot' and 'shutdown -t now -r'</entry>
      <entry label='Suspend command:' name='suspend_command'>If your system uses APM for power management, try 'apm -s' or similar. ACPI users could try 'xset dpms force off; echo 1 > /proc/acpi/sleep'. You'll need a kernel with the correct system compiled in and enabled.</entry>
    </frame>
  </section>
  <section title='Look and Feel'>
    <label help='1'>The mouse, keyboard and display options have moved to the new LookAndFeel application, available from http://rox.sf.net.</label>
  </section>
</options>
