<?xml version='1.0'?>
<options>
  <section title='Window manager'>
    <label help='1'>The window manager is a program which puts title bars and frames on windows. It allows you to move windows around, resize them, close them and so on.</label>
    <wm-combo name='DefaultWM' label='Default window manager'/>
    <spacer/>
    <start-wm/>
  </section>

  <section title='Translation'>
    <frame label='Language'>
      <radio-group name='i18n_translation'>
        <radio label='Danish' value='da'/>
        <radio label='English (no translation)' value='None'/>
        <radio label='Use the LANG environment variable' value='From LANG'/>
      </radio-group>
    </frame>
    <label help='1'>Note that you must save your choices, logout and log back in again before the new settings will take full effect.</label>
  </section>

  <section title='Display'>
    <label help='1'>This setting affects all Gtk+-2 applications, but many applications will ignore it.</label>
    <font name='Gtk/FontName' label='Default Gtk font'>The font used by Gtk+ applications</font>
  </section>

  <section title='Mouse'>
    <slider name='Net/DoubleClickTime' label='Double-click speed: (fast)' end='(slow)'
	    min='100' max='2000'>Time allowed between the two clicks that make up a double click. Make this bigger if you have trouble double-clicking fast enough; set it smaller if two single-clicks sometimes get treated as a double click.
    </slider>
    <spacer/>
    <slider name='accel_threshold' label='Acceleration threshold' min='0' max='20'>Controls how fast you have to move the pointer before the acceleration (below) kicks in.</slider>
    <slider name='accel_factor' label='Acceleration (none)' end='(10x)'
    	    min='10' max='100'>
      When the pointer is moved quickly more than the threshold number of pixels, its speed is multiplied by this number.
    </slider>
  </section>
  
  <section title='Keyboard'>
    <toggle label='Blinking cursor' name='Net/CursorBlink'/>
    <slider label='Speed: (fast)' end='(slow)' name='Net/CursorBlinkTime' fixed='0' min='100' max='2000'>Speed at which the text entry cursor flashes (if flashing is enabled).</slider>
    <toggle name='Gtk/CanChangeAccels'
    	    label='Allow keybindings to be changed from menus'>When this is on, you can set up a short-cut for a menu item by holding to pointer over the menu item and pressing the key. If off, short-cuts cannot be changed.</toggle>
  </section>

  <section title='Messages'>
    <label help='1'>All programs have a 'standard error stream' which they can write text messages to. ROX-Session creates such a connection between itself and every program it starts. It displays all the messages it collects this way briefly on screen.</label>
    <frame label='On-screen message log'>
      <numentry label='Show messages for:' unit='seconds' min='1' max='30' name='log_time_shown'>Number of seconds to display each message for</numentry>
      <spacer/>
      <show-log/>
    </frame>
  </section>
</options>
